<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sur le temps</title>
      <link>/sur-le-temps/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sur-le-temps/</guid>
      <description>I cannot, and oh, if I be entering now into eternity, where there shall be no more distinction of hours, why is it all my business now to tell clocks?
— John Donne
Dès que je me réveille, je me retrouve entouré par des montres, il y en a une accrochée au mur, son visage blanc, aiguilles noirs — immédiatement visible quelle que soit la luminosité — une autre sur l&amp;rsquo;écran de mon ordinateur qui est toujours allumé et bien sûr, celle de mon smartphone qui n&amp;rsquo;est jamais loin de moi, que je dorme ou non.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On title case</title>
      <link>/on-title-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/on-title-case/</guid>
      <description>Natural language is full of rules, conventions, and idiosyncracies, which lend structure and predictability in the otherwise chaotic stream of expressed thoughts. This, in turn, makes communication between speakers easier, as each party more or less knows what to expect when it engages in a conversation. Thus, the utility of rules and conventions as a whole is evident—it is to facilitate communication. However, within any composite body, there are always individual elements that do not contribute to the overall purpose, and are, in a strict sense, useless, but are nevertheless carried along with the flow by their more productive relatives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A balanced approach to Isshin, the Sword Saint</title>
      <link>/sekiro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sekiro/</guid>
      <description>Few fights in Sekiro are more difficult than the combined Genichiro and Sword Saint Isshin. As a consequence, few deathblows feel more rewarding than the one that puts an end to this fight. Other guides either advocate an overly aggressive high risk-high reward strategy, which is very difficult to execute for players who are struggling with the fight to begin with, or else an overly cautious strategy, which tries to get around the actual fight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The best blues albums</title>
      <link>/blues-ranking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blues-ranking/</guid>
      <description>A hundred years ago only blacks in the Deep South were seized by the blues. Now the whole world begins to know them.
— Alan Lomax, The Land Where the Blues Began
I am not sure if Lomax’s statement is intentionally ambiguous. He wrote it in the context of a world that is becoming increasingly anxious, and thus comes to know the blues. However, it is also true that blues music specifically is much more widely known today compared to a hundred years ago.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
